[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403_0201_gates",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403_0201_d_00_Container_gates",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403_0201_gates_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1403_0201_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403_0201_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403_0201_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403_0201_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403_0201_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403_0201_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403_0202_tincturequest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 50,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403_0202_d_00_Container_tincturequest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403_0202_tincturequest_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1403_0202_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403_0202_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403_0202_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403_0202_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403_0202_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403_0202_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1416_0201_sabotage",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1416_0201_d_00_Container_sabotage",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1416_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1416_0201_sabotage_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1416_0201_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1416_0201_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1416_0201_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1416_0201_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1416_0201_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1416_0201_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1416_0202_foreman",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1416_0202_d_00_Container_foreman",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1416_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1416_0202_foreman_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1416_0202_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1416_0202_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1416_0202_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1416_0202_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1416_0202_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1416_0202_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1416_0301_northeast",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 57,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1416_0301_d_00_Container_northeast",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_SurvivalistA",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_09",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1416_0301_northeast_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1416_0301_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1416_0301_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1416_0301_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1416_0301_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1416_0301_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1416_0301_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0201_lights",
        "Type": "SkillProgression",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0201_d_00_Container_lights",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1418_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0201_lights_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1418_0201_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1418_0201_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1418_0201_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1418_0201_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1418_0201_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1418_0201_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0202_azuretears",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0202_d_00_Container_azuretears",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1418_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0202_azuretears_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1418_0202_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1418_0202_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1418_0202_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1418_0202_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1418_0202_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1418_0202_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403_0203_blightpox",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 52,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403_0203_d_00_Container_blightpox",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403_0203_blightpox_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1403_0203_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403_0203_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403_0203_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403_0203_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403_0203_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403_0203_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403_0301_blightstrength",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403_0301_d_00_Container_blightstrength",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_Survivalist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403_0301_blightstrength_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1403_0301_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403_0301_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403_0301_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403_0301_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403_0301_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403_0301_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403_0401_blightmigration",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403_0401_d_00_Container_blightmigration",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_SurvivalistA",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_10",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403_0401_blightmigration_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1403_0401_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403_0401_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403_0401_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403_0401_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403_0401_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403_0401_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1403A_0301_GKW",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1403A_0301_d_00_Container_GKW",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1403_SurvivalistA",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_12",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1403A_0301_GKW_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1403A_0301_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1403A_0301_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1403A_0301_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1403A_0301_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1403A_0301_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1403A_0301_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1413_0201_spriggan",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1413_0201_d_00_Container_spriggan",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1413_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_14",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1413_0201_spriggan_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1413_0201_spriggan_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1413_0201_spriggan_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1413_0201_spriggan_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1413_0201_spriggan_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1413_0201_spriggan_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1413_0201_spriggan_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1414_0101_ToReekwater",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1414_0101_d_00_Container_ToReekwater",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0502_Magistrate",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_13",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1414_0101_ToReekwater_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1414_0101_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1414_0101_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1414_0101_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1414_0101_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1414_0101_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1414_0101_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1426_0101_MoreSabotage",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1426_0101_MoreSabotage_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1426_Foreman",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_15",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1426_0101_BurnEquipment_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1426_0101_MoreSabotage_Title",
        "Description": "@1426_0101_MoreSabotage_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1426_0101_MoreSabotage_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1426_0101_MoreSabotage_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1426_0101_MoreSabotage_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1426_0101_MoreSabotage_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1426_0102_CollapseVault",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1426_0102_CollapseVault_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1426_Foreman",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_16",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_15",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1426_0103_CollapseVault_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1426_0102_CollapseVault_Title",
        "Description": "@1426_0102_CollapseVault_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1426_0102_CollapseVault_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1426_0102_CollapseVault_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1426_0102_CollapseVault_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1426_0102_CollapseVault_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1427_0101_JoinedACult",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 50,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1427_0101_JoinedACult_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1427_CultMother",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1427_0101_JoinedACult_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1427_0101_JoinedACult_Title",
        "Description": "@1427_0101_JoinedACult_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1427_0101_JoinedACult_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1427_0101_JoinedACult_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1427_0101_JoinedACult_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1427_0101_JoinedACult_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1427_0102_Pilgrimmage01",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 52,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1427_0102_Pilgrimmage01_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1428_CultDaughter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_17",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1427_0102_Pilgrimmage01_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1427_0102_Pilgrimmage01_Title",
        "Description": "@1427_0102_Pilgrimmage01_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1427_0102_Pilgrimmage01_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1427_0102_Pilgrimmage01_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1427_0102_Pilgrimmage01_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1427_0102_Pilgrimmage01_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1427_0103_Pilgrimmage02",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 53,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1427_0103_Pilgrimmage02_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1429_CultOfficer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_18",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1427_0103_Pilgrimmage02_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1427_0103_Pilgrimmage02_Title",
        "Description": "@1427_0103_Pilgrimmage02_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1427_0103_Pilgrimmage02_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1427_0103_Pilgrimmage02_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1427_0103_Pilgrimmage02_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1427_0103_Pilgrimmage02_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1427_0104_Oath",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 53,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1427_0104_Oath_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1429_CultOfficer",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_19",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1427_0104_Oath_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1427_0104_Oath_Title",
        "Description": "@1427_0104_Oath_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1427_0104_Oath_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1427_0104_Oath_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1427_0104_Oath_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1427_0104_Oath_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1427_0106_UmbrageTrial",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 57,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1427_0106_UmbrageTrial_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1429_CultOfficer_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_20",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1427_0106_UmbrageTrial_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1427_0106_UmbrageTrial_Title",
        "Description": "@1427_0106_UmbrageTrial_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1427_0106_UmbrageTrial_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1427_0106_UmbrageTrial_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1427_0106_UmbrageTrial_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1427_0106_UmbrageTrial_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1427_0107_HerbalTea",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 57,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1427_0107_HerbalTea_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1429_CultOfficer_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_21",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1427_0107_HerbalTea_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1427_0107_HerbalTea_Title",
        "Description": "@1427_0107_HerbalTea_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1427_0107_HerbalTea_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1427_0107_HerbalTea_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1427_0107_HerbalTea_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1427_0107_HerbalTea_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1427_0108_Wreathes",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1427_0108_Wreathes_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1429_CultOfficer_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_23",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_22",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1427_0108_Wreathes_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1427_0108_Wreathes_Title",
        "Description": "@1427_0108_Wreathes_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1427_0108_Wreathes_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1427_0108_Wreathes_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1427_0108_Wreathes_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1427_0108_Wreathes_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1427_0109_WasteNot",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1427_0109_WasteNot_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1428_CultDaughter_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_24",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_23",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1427_0109_WasteNot_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1427_0109_WasteNot_Title",
        "Description": "@1427_0109_WasteNot_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1427_0109_WasteNot_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1427_0109_WasteNot_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1427_0109_WasteNot_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1427_0109_WasteNot_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1427_0109_DaughtersChoice",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1427_0109_DaughtersChoice_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1428_CultDaughter_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_24",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1427_0109_DaughtersChoice_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1427_0109_DaughtersChoice_Title",
        "Description": "@1427_0109_DaughtersChoice_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1427_0109_DaughtersChoice_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1427_0109_DaughtersChoice_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1427_0109_DaughtersChoice_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1427_0109_DaughtersChoice_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1431_0101_TastyMushrooms",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 52,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1431_0101_TastyMushrooms_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1431_Mycophile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_26",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1431_0101_TastyMushrooms_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1431_0101_TastyMushrooms_Title",
        "Description": "@1431_0101_TastyMushrooms_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1431_0101_TastyMushrooms_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1431_0101_TastyMushrooms_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1431_0101_TastyMushrooms_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1431_0101_TastyMushrooms_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1431_0102_Symbiote",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 52,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1431_0102_Symbiote_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1431_Mycophile_Note",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_27",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_26",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1431_0102_Symbiote_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1431_0102_Symbiote_Title",
        "Description": "@1431_0102_Symbiote_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1431_0102_Symbiote_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1431_0102_Symbiote_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1431_0102_Symbiote_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1431_0102_Symbiote_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1431_0103_BeRightBack",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 52,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1431_0103_BeRightBack_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1431_Mycophile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_28",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_27",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1431_0103_BeRightBack_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1431_0103_BeRightBack_Title",
        "Description": "@1431_0103_BeRightBack_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1431_0103_BeRightBack_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1431_0103_BeRightBack_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1431_0103_BeRightBack_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1431_0103_BeRightBack_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1431_0104_Mycelium",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1431_0104_Mycelium_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1431_Mycophile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_29",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_28",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1431_0104_Mycelium_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1431_0104_Mycelium_Title",
        "Description": "@1431_0104_Mycelium_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1431_0104_Mycelium_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1431_0104_Mycelium_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1431_0104_Mycelium_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1431_0104_Mycelium_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1432_0101_Medicine",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1432_0101_Medicine_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1432_Homesteader",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_30",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1432_0101_Medicine_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1432_0101_Medicine_Title",
        "Description": "@1432_0101_Medicine_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1432_0101_Medicine_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1432_0101_Medicine_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1432_0101_Medicine_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1432_0101_Medicine_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1432_0102_DryadThieves",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1432_0102_DryadThieves_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1432_Homesteader_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_31",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_30",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1432_0102_DryadThieves_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1432_0102_DryadThieves_Title",
        "Description": "@1432_0102_DryadThieves_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1432_0102_DryadThieves_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1432_0102_DryadThieves_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1432_0102_DryadThieves_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1432_0102_DryadThieves_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1432_0103_LostDog",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 57,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1432_0103_LostDog_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1433_AEDog_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_32",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_31",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1432_0103_LostDog_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1432_0103_LostDog_Title",
        "Description": "@1432_0103_LostDog_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1432_0103_LostDog_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1432_0103_LostDog_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1432_0103_LostDog_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1432_0103_LostDog_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1432_0104_FoundDog",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 57,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1432_0104_FoundDog_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1432_Homesteader_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_33",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_32",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1432_0104_FoundDog_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1432_0104_FoundDog_Title",
        "Description": "@1432_0104_FoundDog_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1432_0104_FoundDog_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1432_0104_FoundDog_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1432_0104_FoundDog_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1432_0104_FoundDog_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1435_0101_PutItBack",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1435_0101_PutItBack_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1435_SirenDryad",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_34",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_33",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1435_0101_PutItBack_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1435_0101_PutItBack_Title",
        "Description": "@1435_0101_PutItBack_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1435_0101_PutItBack_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1435_0101_PutItBack_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1435_0101_PutItBack_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1435_0101_PutItBack_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1435_0102_PopBlossoms",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 59,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1435_0102_PopBlossoms_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1435_SirenDryad_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_35",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_34",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1435_0102_PopBlossoms_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1435_0102_PopBlossoms_Title",
        "Description": "@1435_0102_PopBlossoms_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1435_0102_PopBlossoms_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1435_0102_PopBlossoms_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1435_0102_PopBlossoms_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1435_0102_PopBlossoms_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1435_0103_WayUpHigh",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1435_0103_WayUpHigh_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1435_SirenDryad_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_36",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_35",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1435_0102_WayUpHigh_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1435_0102_WayUpHigh_Title",
        "Description": "@1435_0102_WayUpHigh_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1435_0102_WayUpHigh_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1435_0102_WayUpHigh_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1435_0102_WayUpHigh_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1435_0102_WayUpHigh_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1434_0101_DestroyBlooms",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 57,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1434_0101_DestroyBlooms_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1434_SirenRanger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_37",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_21",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1434_0101_DestroyBlooms_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1434_0101_DestroyBlooms_Title",
        "Description": "@1434_0101_DestroyBlooms_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1434_0101_DestroyBlooms_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1434_0101_DestroyBlooms_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1434_0101_DestroyBlooms_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1434_0101_DestroyBlooms_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1434_0102_ClearPath",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 57,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1434_0102_ClearPath_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1434_SirenRanger_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_38",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_37",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1434_0102_ClearPath_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1434_0102_ClearPath_Title",
        "Description": "@1434_0102_ClearPath_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1434_0102_ClearPath_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1434_0102_ClearPath_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1434_0102_ClearPath_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1434_0102_ClearPath_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1434_0103_Pyre",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1434_0103_Pyre_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1434_SirenRanger_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_39",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_38",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1434_0103_Pyre_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1434_0103_Pyre_Title",
        "Description": "@1434_0103_Pyre_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1434_0103_Pyre_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1434_0103_Pyre_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1434_0103_Pyre_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1434_0103_Pyre_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1434_0104_OutOfHisMisery",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 58,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1434_0104_OutOfHisMisery_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "1435_SirenDryad_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "14_Quest_40",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "14_Quest_36",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1434_0103_OutOfHisMisery_Success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@1434_0103_OutOfHisMisery_Title",
        "Description": "@1434_0103_OutOfHisMisery_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1434_0103_OutOfHisMisery_Start_Prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1434_0103_OutOfHisMisery_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1434_0103_OutOfHisMisery_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1434_0103_OutOfHisMisery_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false,
        "ReleaseVersion": "Quest_Supplement_Edengrove"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0501_ClamorousVox",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_00_Containter_weaponwrapperquest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_1501_ClamorousVoxSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0501_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0501_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1420_0501_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1420_0501_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1420_0501_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1420_0501_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0502_CVOne",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_01_01_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0502_CVOneSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0502_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0502_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0503_CVTwo",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_01_02_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0503_CVTwoSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0503_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0503_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0504_CVThree",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_01_03_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0504_CVThreeSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0504_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0504_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0505_CVFour",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_01_04_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0505_CVFourSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0505_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0505_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0506_CVFive",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_02_01_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0506_CVFiveSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0506_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0506_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0507_CVSix",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_02_02_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0507_CVSixSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0507_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0507_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0508_CVSeven",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_02_03_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0508_CVSevenSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0508_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0508_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1420_0509_CVEight",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1420_0501_d_02_04_weaponwrapperquest_questComplete4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_ClamorousVox_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1420_0509_CVEightSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1420_0509_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1420_0509_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0201_Torrent",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_00_TorrentContainer_weaponwrapperquest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0201_TorrentSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0201_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0201_b_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1421_0201_c_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1421_0201_c_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1421_0201_e_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1421_0201_f_Complete",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0202_TorOne",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_01_01_weaponwrapperquest_TorOne",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0202_TorOneSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0202_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0202_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0203_TorTwo",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_01_02_weaponwrapperquest_TorTwo",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0203_TorTwoSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0203_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0203_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0204_TorThree",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_01_03_weaponwrapperquest_TorThree",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0204_TorThreeSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0204_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0204_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0205_TorFour",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_01_04_weaponwrapperquest_TorFour",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0205_TorFourSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0205_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0205_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0206_TorFive",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_02_01_weaponwrapperquest_TorFive",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0206_TorFiveSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0206_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0206_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0207_TorSix",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_02_02_weaponwrapperquest_TorSix",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0207_TorSixSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0207_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0207_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0208_TorSeven",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_02_03_weaponwrapperquest_TorSeven",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0208_TorSevenSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0208_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0208_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1421_0209_TorEight",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1421_0201_d_02_04_weaponwrapperquest_TorEight",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Torrent_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1421_0209_TorEightSuccess",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1421_0209_a_Title",
        "Description": "@1421_0209_b_Description",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0201_Reformation",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0201_d_00_container_Reformation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0201_Reformation_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0201_Reformation_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0201_Reformation_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1419_0201_Reformation_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0201_Reformation_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0201_Reformation_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0201_Reformation_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0202_d_00_container_Reformation_metalsraw",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0202_Reformation_metalsraw_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0203_d_00_container_Reformation_essencebalanced",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0203_Reformation_essencebalanced_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0204_d_00_container_Reformation_polishpure",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0204_Reformation_polishpure_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0205_d_00_container_Reformation_wieldertested",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0205_Reformation_wieldertested_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0206_d_00_container_Reformation_bindingstight",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0206_Reformation_bindingstight_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0207_d_00_container_Reformation_firesstoked",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0207_Reformation_firesstoked_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0208_d_00_container_Reformation_hafthewn",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0208_Reformation_hafthewn_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1419_0209_d_00_container_Reformation_gripsecured",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Reformation_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1419_0209_Reformation_gripsecured_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0101_RD_00",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0101_RD_00_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0101_RD_00_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_00_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_00_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1418_0101_RD_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1418_0101_RD_00_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@1418_0101_RD_00_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1418_0101_RD_00_complete_available_response",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0102_RD_01",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0102_RD_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0102_RD_01_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_01_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_01_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0103_RD_02",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0103_RD_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0103_RD_02_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_02_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_02_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0104_RD_03",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0104_RD_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0104_RD_03_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_03_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_03_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0105_RD_04",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0105_RD_04_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0105_RD_04_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_04_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_04_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0106_RD_05",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0106_RD_05_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0106_RD_05_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_05_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_05_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0107_RD_06",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0107_RD_06_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0107_RD_06_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_06_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_06_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0108_RD_07",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0108_RD_07_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0108_RD_07_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_07_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_07_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1418_0109_RD_08",
        "Type": "EpicEquipment",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "1418_0109_RD_08_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_RooksDefense_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1418_0109_RD_08_success",
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@1418_0101_RD_08_objective_title",
        "Description": "@1418_0101_RD_08_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1401_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1401_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1402_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1402_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1403_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1403_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1404_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1404_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1405_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1405_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1406_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1406_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1407_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1407_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1408_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1408_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1409_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1409_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1410_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1410_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1401_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1401_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1402_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1402_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1403_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1403_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1404_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1404_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1405_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1405_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1406_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1406_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1407_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1407_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1408_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1408_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1409_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1409_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1410_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1410_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1401_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1401_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1402_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1402_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1403_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1403_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1404_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1404_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1405_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1405_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1406_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1406_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1407_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1407_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1408_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1408_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1409_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1409_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1410_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1410_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1461_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1461_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1462_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1462_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1463_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1463_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1464_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1464_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1465_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1465_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1466_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1466_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1467_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1467_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1468_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1468_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1469_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1469_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_1470_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_1470_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1461_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1461_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1462_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1462_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1463_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1463_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1464_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1464_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1465_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1465_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1466_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1466_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1467_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1467_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1468_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1468_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1469_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1469_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_1470_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_1470_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1461_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1461_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1462_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1462_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1463_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1463_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1464_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1464_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1465_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1465_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1466_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1466_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1467_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1467_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1468_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1468_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1469_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1469_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_1470_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_1470_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Spy_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Poach_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_14_PVP_Control_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_H_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_H_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 14,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_EXP_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_EXP_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_EXP_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_EXP_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_14_EXP_03_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_14_EXP_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "Repeatable": 0,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": false
    }
]